{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2375","name":"New Robert's Coney Island Inc.","address":"12701 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205","owner":"Gjon Gjini","licenseNumber":"056536","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-82.99453,42.43494","geojson":{"id":"2375","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.99452718,42.434943283]},"properties":{"name":"New Robert's Coney Island Inc.","owner":"Gjon Gjini","address":"12701 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"056536","establishmentid":"2375","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"4/14/2015"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3497","name":"Prince Pizza Chicken & Ribs","address":"13000 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"1167","name":"Fleming Elementary","address":"18501 Waltham St","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"951","name":"Turning Point Academy","address":"12300 Linnhurst","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"1171","name":"Pulaski Elementary / Middle School","address":"19725 Strasburg St","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"4772","name":"Me & My Girls Soul Food","address":"11831 E Seven Mile Rd. ","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"5338","name":"R & D One Stop Meals","address":"11811 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"940","name":"Osborn Senior High School","address":"11600 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"51622880","name":"Trix Academy","address":"20045 Joann St","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"3321","name":"Brenda Scott Middle School","address":"18400 Hoover Rd","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"5411","name":"Royal Fish & Chicken Inc.","address":"11429 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48234"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"50720","inspectionDate":"2020-02-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Unprotected","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48374","inspectionDate":"2019-07-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"TOP LOADER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-07-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-07-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-07-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44582","inspectionDate":"2018-12-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-12-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"42495","inspectionDate":"2018-05-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\r\n\r\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-05-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"TOP LOADER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F thawed or partially thawed","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store under refrigeration."}]},{"inspectionid":"40643","inspectionDate":"2017-10-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"TOP LOADER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"TOP LOADER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-10-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"39398","inspectionDate":"2017-06-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"37247","inspectionDate":"2016-11-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"TOP LOADER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-11-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"TOP LOADER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep covered."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER & FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2375"}}